<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Welcome!</title>
    <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Welcome!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 22:30:17 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.raveen.ca/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
<<<<<<< HEAD
      <title>XYZ Gripper Robot</title>
=======
      <title>Re-learning Python</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 10:24:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/python/</guid>
      <description>The Goal The goal of this project is to get better with Python. I learned Python in my first year programming class and used a little bit over the years, but I would hesitate to say I have a &amp;ldquo;functional&amp;rdquo; knowledge of the language. My goal with this project is to develop a better foundation so I can apply it better. To start I am going to be working through ForrestKnight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Open Source Python Course&amp;rdquo; (https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gripper</title>
>>>>>>> test-branch
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/gripper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 23:57:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/gripper/</guid>
      <description>Completed: April 2022
This was my final year capstone project. The client for this project was a material sciences professor. For his research, his group completes many compressions tests of 3D printed components, so our project revolved around removing tedious parts of his project. There were different aspects of the testing process that we could have focused on, but we decided to make a robot that automates the queueing, loading and removal of test samples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gearhand</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/gearhand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 21:01:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/gearhand/</guid>
      <description>Completed: April 2017
This was my first year group design project. The goal of the project was to design a gear train that would move two fingers open and close. We were constrained to a given area and we were also given a specific gear ratio that our train had to be.
There was a lot to learn from this project. This was my first design project so I expected to have hiccups, those hiccups turned out to bite the group in the butt later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walkingrobot</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/walkingrobot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 21:01:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/walkingrobot/</guid>
      <description>Completed: April 2018
This project was in my second year, in the MECHENG 2C04 design course. The goal of the project was to design a moving robot that didn&amp;rsquo;t use wheels. The movement would be driven by motors but we had to create an alternative mechanism for the robot to move. The robot would also have to be able to walk over an obstacle of unknown height.
My group decided to use a gear train with rotating legs to allow the robot to move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropper Seat Post Design Project</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/dropperseat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 21:01:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/dropperseat/</guid>
      <description>Completed: April 2020
This project was for my third year, in the MECHENG 3E05 design course. The goal of the project was the design a product. The groups were given free reign on what to design, but an important aspect of the project was to make sure the design was justified using engineering calculations. The project was evaluated based on how well the calculations account for issues like buckling and bolt calculations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Balancing Robot</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/balancingrobot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 21:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/balancingrobot/</guid>
      <description>Completed: July 2021
This was my first personal project. During the summer, I decided I wanted to try making a self-balancing robot. I thought it would be a good introductory project to apply what I learned from my control systems course from the previous school term as well as learn a little more about arduinos and using motors.
The chassis was made using 3D printed pieces that were attached together with thermal set inserts and fasteners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assembly Lab</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/assemblylab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 21:00:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/assemblylab/</guid>
      <description>Completed: August 2021
This project was completed while working as an Educational Assistant for the Mechanical Engineering Department at McMaster. The purpose of this lab was to teach students about design techniques when 3D printing and laser cutting. I was tasked with designing a car which utilized different kinds of parts or fasteners. Some parts were purposefully designed to be combursome to highlight the importance of design for assembly. The students then would assemble the kit and comment on what designed components worked well and didn&amp;rsquo;t work well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pokeball</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/pokeball/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 21:00:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/pokeball/</guid>
      <description>Updates coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Website</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 21:00:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/projects/website/</guid>
      <description>I will be using this page a working post for my website, I&amp;rsquo;ll mention updates and future plans with the website here.
This is the repo for the site (https://github.com/raveenapp/main-site.git)
History of This Website Completed: October 2022
I&amp;rsquo;ve always liked the idea of having my own little piece of the internet (hence why its the tag line on home page). But I didn&amp;rsquo;t really commit to having my own website until I watched a CollegeInfoGeek video on it in 2017 (https://youtu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
