<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Welcome!</title>
    <link>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 16:43:23 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.raveen.ca/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Master&#39;s Log - 0</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/masterslog-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 16:43:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/masterslog-0/</guid>
      <description>While on the bus a month ago, I thought it would be cool to keep a written blog of my experiences while completing my masters. This would be an on-going &amp;ldquo;series&amp;rdquo; of posts that would share what I&amp;rsquo;m working on, any tools I&amp;rsquo;m using, my workflow, organization system or anything of the sort. I&amp;rsquo;d like to make a post every few weeks (but let&amp;rsquo;s see if that happens).
Current Plan I don&amp;rsquo;t start it until January so this plan is completely based on speaking to other grad students and reading online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2022 - Update</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/2022decupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 23:33:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/2022decupdate/</guid>
      <description>November came and went! Overall, it was a great month. Work went fine, I got to travel for a week and slowly chipping away at my goals. Just another month left in the year. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how this goes!
Fitness Keep current workout schedule Kept my 4-day schedule all month except for the week I went travelling, will continue this into December Learning Pickup Python Course and do a little every night Not a lot of progress made here, hard to commit time when I get home pretty late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being Okay with Insignificance</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/insignificance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 20:40:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/insignificance/</guid>
      <description>Over the last few years, I&amp;rsquo;ve been grappling with the idea of mundanity and finding meaning. A reoccurring thought I have is that in the macro sense, life is meaningless. To go into more detail, no matter what I do or what happens in my life, I and everyone I love will eventually die and be forgotten. And even if I make a name for myself, my legacy will be forgotten in a few generations too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2022 - Update</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/2022novupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 14:02:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/2022novupdate/</guid>
      <description>I would like to start making post reflecting on the upcoming month. Here, I&amp;rsquo;d plan my goals for the month, and then at the end of the month, I&amp;rsquo;d re-evaluate my progress. This way I can see if goals I set are realistic and achieveable or do I need to change my expectations.
Fitness:
Keep current workout schedule Learning:
Pickup Python Course and do a little every night Hobbies:
Complete PSTAR exam to start process to regain flying currency Arts:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s the point of this website?</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/this_website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:33:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/this_website/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve explained the history of the development of this website and I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned on my about page that this website is a &amp;ldquo;mixture of a portfolio and a blog site&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m going to take this post to explain in more detail my motivations for this site.
There was once what I like to call the &amp;ldquo;golden era of the internet&amp;rdquo;, which deserves a post of its own. But basically, from like the 90s to the late 2000s, everyone had their own website or forum to share their ideas and it was very decentralized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First_post</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 21:49:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/posts/first_post/</guid>
      <description>This is a test post.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
