<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About Me on Welcome!</title>
    <link>https://www.raveen.ca/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About Me on Welcome!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 20:28:33 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.raveen.ca/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tech I use</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/about/tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 20:48:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/about/tech/</guid>
      <description>This is the tech I am using, I&amp;rsquo;ll probably add more detail after time. And yes, I did name them all after my favourite Pokemon.
Daily Drivers Mamoswine: Lenevo Thinkpad T470s (running Manjaro) - primary laptop Rotom: iPhone 13 Pro - phone Phantump: Airpod (Gen 2) - earbuds Wooper: iPad Air (Gen 2) - tablet </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Library</title>
      <link>https://www.raveen.ca/about/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 20:48:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.raveen.ca/about/library/</guid>
      <description>This is a personal collection of things I&amp;rsquo;ve watched and read since I started tracking it.
2022 TV Shows Tokyo Revengers Season 1 Demon Slayer Season 2 Brooklyn 99 Season 8 Attack on Titan Season 4 Given Criminal Minds Season 1-3 Mr. Robot The Boys Season 3 Stranger Things Season 4 Ozark Ousama Ranking Vinland Saga Season 1 Monster Chainsaw Man (NW) Blue Lock (NW) My Hero Academia Season 6 (NW) Mob Psycho III (NW) Movies My Hero Academia: World Hero&amp;rsquo;s Mission Jujistu Kaison: Movie 0 Pulp Fiction The Wind Rises 13 Lives Free Guy Top Gun Books Look Back Goodbye, Eri Fire Punch Vagabond The Acid Room 2021 TV Shows My Hero Academia Season 5 Invincible JJK The Boys OPM Season 2 Violet Evergarden Neon Genesis Evangelion Attack on Titan Season 4 Mob Psycho Season 1 and Season 2 Squid Games Season 1 Movies Weathering with You I want to eat your Pancreas Dune End of Evangelion Demon Slayer: Mugen Train Books Speaker of the Dead Children of the Mind A Man Called Ove Berserk Sweat and Soap </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
